hey everybody welcome to this a2 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to train your listening and
comprehension as I speak so today I'm
going to talk about sports this is a
topic that some of you might really like
and some of you might not like it at all
I've always been an athletic person so I
like sports when I was young I played a
ton of sports I tried playing almost all
of the major sports during my childhood
one of the first sports I played was
t-ball you might not have heard of this
sport before because it's only for small
children
I played t-ball when I was like four or
five years old it's like baseball but
easier and simpler after t-ball I
started playing soccer in the US many
children play soccer but not many adults
play soccer soccer isn't as popular in
the US as it is in other countries I
also played baseball tennis and
basketball when I was young out of all
these sports my favorite sport was
definitely basketball I continued
playing basketball until I was 17 and
then I stopped I was pretty tall when I
was young so I had an advantage when I
played basketball the other kids were
shorter than me I was the tallest person
on my middle-school team this means that
I could score pretty easily but when I
was in high school the other kids grew
and then I wasn't much taller than them
so I couldn't score easily anymore maybe
that's why I quit basketball I played
tennis a lot when I was young too my
whole family really likes tennis so my
parents made me play when I was young I
don't think I liked it that much when I
started but later I began to like it
more I was actually pretty good I took
many lessons in played in some different
tennis tournaments but I quit tennis
because I was more focused on basket
also when I was 16 I wanted to play
football American football you might not
know much about American football but
it's probably the most popular sport for
men in the u.s. well I also really liked
football and I wanted to play on my high
school team I trained with them for some
months but I wasn't that serious about
it the team practiced a lot like every
day and I couldn't do that so in the end
I didn't play after high school I
started playing golf golf is one of the
funnest sports in my opinion it's super
hard maybe the hardest sport of all but
that's what makes it so addicting you
feel really proud when you hit a good
shot because you know how difficult it
is to do that it's also really
frustrating when you mess up
so sometimes golf is not fun but when
you have a good day on the course
there's nothing like it it's so
addicting nowadays I don't really play
any sports anymore I honestly don't have
a lot of time to play sports and I don't
have the same motivation that I had when
I was young now I'm more motivated to do
other things but I still enjoy playing
sports from time to time now let's talk
about watching sports
some people prefer watching sports
rather than playing them I used to love
watching sports I was probably a little
too obsessed my favorite football team
when I was younger was the Seattle
Seahawks and I watched every one of
their games I would get really excited
when they made it to the playoffs and I
celebrated like crazy when they won the
Super Bowl but I think I spent too much
time and energy being a football fan
nowadays I don't really watch football
anymore I was also a big LA Lakers fan
when I was younger I was lucky because I
got to see them win the championship
five times when I was a kid I used to
dream of playing for the lake
when I got older these days the only
sport I watch is soccer I think I
started getting into soccer when I was
an adult like I said before I played
when I was a kid but I always preferred
other sports but as an adult soccer is
definitely my favorite sport besides the
normal sports I've also done some
extreme sports like skateboarding and
snowboarding I used to skateboard a lot
when I was in high school and I also
filmed some skate videos with my friends
I would say that I was never really good
though I always liked watching other
people do tricks that I couldn't do as
for snowboarding I've only gone three
times but I found it really fun the
first time was not good because I fell
down dozens of times but the second and
third time were much better once I
started to understand how to move
correctly it became fun I can't wait to
go snowboarding again okay that's all
for today leave a comment and tell me
what your favorite sport is I'll see you
next video
[Music]